There are no heroes. Only rebels.
Rebel Moon - Part One: A Child of Fire is a science fiction,
action, adventure film directed by Zack Snyder.
When the ruthless forces of the Motherworld threaten a quiet farming village on a
distant moon, a mysterious outsider becomes its best hope for survival.
Kora, played by Sofia Boutella.
Gunnar, played by Michiel Huisman.
Atticus Noble, played by Ed Skrein.
Titus, played by Djimon Hounsou.
Nemesis, played by Bae Doona.
Tarak, played by Staz Nair.
Rebel Moon – Part One: A Child of Fire, or simply Rebel Moon, is a 2023 American epic space opera film
directed by Zack Snyder from a screenplay he co-wrote with Kurt Johnstad and Shay Hatten.
Its ensemble cast features Sofia Boutella, Djimon Hounsou, Ed Skrein, Michiel
Huisman, Bae Doona, Ray Fisher, Charlie Hunnam, and Anthony Hopkins.
The film is set in a fictional galaxy ruled by the imperialistic Motherworld,
whose military, the Imperium, threatens a village on the moon Veldt.
Kora, a former Imperium soldier, ventures on a quest to recruit warriors from across the
galaxy to make a stand against the Imperium before they return to Veldt.
Following a limited theatrical release on December 15, 2023,
Rebel Moon was released by Netflix on December 22.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.
A sequel, Rebel Moon – Part Two: The Scargiver, released on April 19, 2024.
An R-rated director's cut, titled Rebel Moon – Chapter One:
Chalice of Blood, was released on August 2, 2024.
The film explores themes of rebellion, space war,
space, female protagonist, militarism.
The tone is thought_provoking.